(Episode 8)
I'm not sure if it's the right thing
to write this letter to you.
But Jun Seo,
I want you to know that
my life also became
more beautiful than anything...
after meeting you.
I am...
so happy just to be close to you enough
so I can see you around.
I wanted to tell you that, too.
No matter what happens,
we'll never be apart,
and now...
we have to go back
to being brother and sister.
And...
when written in a letter,
everything seems too easy,
which makes me feel duped.
Jun Seo,
I love you.
With a different meaning of the same word.
So I'm happy.
Eun Seo.
What did you buy so much?
Isn't it heavy? I'll carry it.
It's been a long time.
When you press the shoot button,
the shutter will go off
after five seconds.
Okay.
You look great in these photos, as usual.
Do not lose them, all right?
Where should I put them?
Should I put them in my wallet?
Wait.
You don't have Yu Mi's photo.
Don't I?
Just put them in for now.
When you have Yu Mi's photo,
you can put mine in with hers.
You're saying that so you don't have
to put them in either, right?
You got me.
What?
Did you say you want
to live with plants or dogs?
Is that really your dream?
Goldfish would be good, too.
You have no idea how scary I can be.
I never have any living creatures near me.
I didn't ask you to take care of them.
I mean if a man takes care of those,
I would get married to him.
Is that so?
All right, good luck with that.
You'll never do that.
I spent too much.
What is it? Is it your cashbook?
Do you need more money?
Then I can...
Don't say another word.
I am sorry.
All the skills I've practiced are...
so useless.
Let me see what you're drawing secretly.
No.
No?
Why are you all like that?
What do you mean?
Jun Seo didn't let me see his drawings.
He didn't?
He might draw something
that can't be seen.
Such as...
his secret lover.
Excuse me.
Marry me.
Marry me, Choi Eun Seo.
Hello.
Are you waiting for someone?
I called you too late, didn't I?
No, I was going to call you, actually.
Why? Did something happen?
Well.
I wanted to make kimchi stew, but...
I wasn't sure when to add kimchi.
So...
I see.
Do you want me to tell you?
Or write it down?
No, it's okay.
Why are you making kimchi stew,
by the way?
I just...
I don't have class tomorrow, so...
I'm planning to go on a one-day hike.
Do you remember the cabin
we used to visit? I'm going there.
Really?
Are you going with Yu Mi?
No, I'm going alone.
Do you want to join me?
I...
Right.
- Yu Mi.
- Tae Seok.
Marry me, Choi Eun Seo.
Marry me.
Mom keeps asking me
when we're getting married.
What should I tell her?
Do you want to come?
Yes.
We probably can't go together
once you get married.
And also, it's just for a day, right?
Yes.
It's just siblings going on a hike
after a long time.
It is, right?
Yes, you should stay home today.
Why? Are you going somewhere?
Yes.
I have a friend coming from Seoul.
You know Seung Taek,
who studied with me in the U.S.
Yes.
I'll call you when I'm back.
Right.
Yoon Jun Seo.
What? A friend of yours
is coming from Seoul?
Are you going home?
What time is it now?
Wait for me. I'll take you home.
No.
I'm going with Kang Hee.
So, I would rather you didn't come.
I will be back soon
after meeting Mom and Dad.
You're lying, aren't you?
Your eyes just widened.
I'm just kidding.
Have a good time.
Please give them my regards.
I'll see you later.
And...
on your way back,
get me some squid from the store
near your house.
All right?
Okay.
Kimchi stew tastes much better
when made with stir-fried kimchi.
- I agree.
- Right?
You got me.
You said you didn't know how to make it.
Did you lie?
No.
To say I called you
because I missed you...
is embarrassing.
I see.
I'm hungry. Let's hurry.
Okay, I got it. It's almost done.
Give it a bit more time.
What is that?
- What?
- It's raining, Eun Seo.
Take them inside.
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
He never puts things in the right way.
What a mess.
Did you come already?
Tae Seok?
Is Jun Seo not here?
He went to meet his friend.
What brings you here?
Where is Eun Seo?
She went out with her friend.
You're just like me.
- Have dinner with me.
- Okay.
It's pouring.
I know.
Hello.
Who is it?
The management office? Yes.
What?
When will it be repaired?
All right.
Yes, I understand.
What's wrong?
What should we do?
I don't think you can go back today.
So, then...
I think we need to spend the night here.
Just the two of us?
I lied.
I didn't tell Tae Seok
I came here with you.
Was I wrong?
No.
So did I. I lied, too.
I didn't intend to, but I lied.
They're getting late.
They are, indeed.
Her parents must be holding her back.
Her parents?
Do you mean Jun Seo's parents?
They're in Seoul now.
Is Eun Seo...
There must be some miscommunication.
You might even make a trip for nothing.
Eun Seo?
Where are you?
I'm at my parents' house.
They won't let me go because it's raining.
I will sleep over here.
Are you sleeping over there?
Are you? I see.
Hello.
Jun Seo.
All right.
You'll come back early, won't you?
Are you going to spend the night there?
I see.
All right.
You sleep over there.
You are sleeping over there.
It reminds me of old times.
When I had a nightmare,
I always went to your room and cried.
Then, I slept on your bed,
and you slept on the floor.
Do you remember that?
I remember everything now.
Your beautiful sister, Yoon Eun Seo.
Yes.
I'll be your beautiful sister forever.
Of course.
I think being siblings is much better.
Once we're siblings,
we'll be siblings forever.
You're right.
Yes.
We're siblings for the rest of our lives.
But what if I die first?
Then who is going to take care of you?
No. I'll die before you do.
You shouldn't die leaving me alone.
You shouldn't. Okay?
I don't want to lose you again.
I don't want to lose you...
more than once in my life.
So,
I'll die first.
I understand.
I'll be by your side when you die.
I'll hold your hand,
and I'll laugh with you.
I won't let you go alone.
I'll always be with you.
Don't worry, okay?
Yes.
Okay.
You...
promise me.
When did you know?
I've recently found out.
I've known for a long time.
It's been so hard.
Do you think they're serious?
Tae Seok, do you believe in fate?
No.
I only believe in myself.
I didn't use to believe in fate, but...
I've been thinking that...
there might be fates
that are predetermined.
Don't you think we are going against fate?
Are we going against the fates
of Jun Seo and Eun Seo?
So what? What if we do?
It's my fate, too.
Mine is much more powerful.
I will show them that.
Sin Yu Mi, don't let up.
You need to get married
to Jun Seo and be happy.
I can't let up.
I'm leaving.
You came.
When did you come?
I just came.
I guess you had drinks with your friend.
So, I made porridge for you.
Did you have a good time?
Yes, I did.
Hello.
Excuse me.
You came back.
I came back early, didn't I?
This is for you.
You asked me to.
Do you get it now?
Is it him?
That's how it is.
Tae Seok, I think we need more beer.
Can you bring some?
Yes, just a moment.
Who left this here?
Is it Jun Seo's?
Tae Seok, I think you drank too much.
What?
I haven't drunk much.
I'm in the best mood now.
It's so good.
Let me have another one.
Tae Seok.
Yes?
Yes, Eun Seo.
What are you all doing?
Let's have a drink.
Come on, have a drink.
This round is very important.
This round is for...
our wedding announcement.
Tae Seok.
Right.
Somebody said we need to plant a tree
to get married.
A wedding? What are you talking about?
What does a tree have to do
with a wedding?
Eun Seo said that...
she wanted to be a tree
if she were to be born again.
That's interesting. A tree?
I see.
She did.
That was...
something Eun Seo said when she was young.
Was it?
You have so many secrets.
We have lots of secrets.
Don't we?
Stop it, Tae Seok. That is enough.
What did I do?
I didn't do anything wrong for sure.
I don't have any secrets,
not even a small one.
What about you, Eun Seo?
Do you have a secret
that you can't say out loud?
- Stop it.
- You don't get to yell at me.
Stop, all of you. What are you doing?
Is having secrets that bad?
I like having them.
Because I can keep them in my heart,
so I feel fulfilled.
Is that a wrong thing?
To feel fulfilled?
Do you feel fulfilled?
What is wrong, Tae Seok?
The secret. Can I tell you what it is?
The secret is that...
you like Jun Seo.
Han Tae Seok.
Do you want me to say that again?
Choi Eun Seo...
likes Yoon Jun Seo.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
In order to get Eun Seo,
I could even kill you.
Tae Seok.
That is the way in which I love Eun Seo.
What is your way?
Did you call for me?
I will clean up.
I am sorry.
I am so sorry, Tae Seok.
I believed it was going to work.
It's my fault.
It was so hard for me,
and because it was so hard, I used you.
I was so wrong.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Then, don't hurt me.
Tae Seok.
I...
I don't care if you love Jun Seo.
Just like this moment...
Even if you break my heart so much,
I don't care.
I don't care about anything.
All I need is you.
You are all I need.
Excuse me.
How can I help you?
Eun Seo... are you Choi Eun Seo's mother?
My name is Han Tae Seok.
Mom.
You?
Is this the guy who ran away
with Eun Seo the other day?
You, it was all because of you...
I have something to tell you.
Can I come in?
Yes, please come in.
Look, what are you doing?
I am dating Choi Eun Seo.
I need to talk with you about Eun Seo.
You!
What have you done,
how dare you come here?
What did you do to my sister?
What did you do?
Do you think you can do whatever
because you're the director of the hotel?
Do you want to get away with it like this?
Do you think money can solve everything?
It's not something
you can settle with money.
Get out. You get out of here.
Mom, I'm telling you
he's done something to Eun Seo...
That is not why I am here.
I came to tell you
I want to marry Eun Seo.
I want to get married to Eun Seo.
Please give me your permission.
I promise I will make her happy.
Do you want to get married to Eun Seo?
Are you sure?
Have you talked with Eun Seo already?
Mom, what is there to talk about?
He said he wanted to get married to her.
I mean, that's...
I look forward to it.
(Director Han Tae Seok)
Have you met Sin Ae?
I am sorry.
I have met her without asking you.
I am sorry. I have met Eun Seo, too.
I am sorry.
The reason I came here...
is because someone wants to marry Eun Seo.
Is that someone Tae Seok?
What?
You know that already. You know.
Yes, I have known about it since...
he is my son Jun Seo's friend.
That is good.
What is he like?
Is he a nice person?
No, I don't need to ask anything but this.
He wants to get married to Eun Seo.
If you were me, would you say "yes?"
Eun Seo...
has grown enough to get married.
She has.
I am sorry.
While she was growing up that much,
I couldn't do much for her.
I was out of my mind. I really was.
I was so selfish.
I should've sent her with you.
I couldn't even send her to college.
I am the crazy one. Me.
No, that's not true.
She has grown up pretty and kind.
Thank you so much...
for raising her to be a beautiful woman.
I know it is late, but...
Eun Seo...
Can you take her?
What?
She has the luck
to have a good man, but...
what would happen
if his family learns how I live?
Her brother being a gangster,
and her mother being...
I think...
Eun Seo was never meant to be my daughter.
It has been too much for me to raise her.
I meant to send her away every moment.
Please take her,
so that she can get married...
to a proper man.
You must adopt her,
and if she becomes
Professor Yoon's daughter,
his family won't be against her
getting married to him.
Please.
I am begging you.
Are you sure?
Do you really mean it?
Please.
I am begging you.
Please take Eun Seo.
Please.
Mom.
What are you doing?
Why are you sending Eun Seo to my family?
Why don't you say something?
What are you thinking?
Do you want this?
No, who wants this cola?
Don't you remember that?
When you were little,
even before you were in elementary school,
you kept asking me to buy cola,
and I said "no."
You ended up getting caught stealing one.
What?
What are you talking about?
Although I hit you out of temper,
I felt terrible.
I couldn't afford a 15-cent can of cola,
and had made my only daughter
a shoplifter.
What could I do?
It was your fate to meet a mother
who didn't even have 15 cents.
It's also Eun Seo's fate that...
the switching occurred and she met me,
who couldn't afford college tuition.
So?
Are you telling me to do nothing
about Eun Seo coming to my family?
It is no one's fault.
You and Eun Seo were switched,
and had to struggle.
It was just all of your fates.
Now, you and Eun Seo
get along with each other...
like sisters.
No, I can't.
I can't do that.
No, I won't do that.
Why should I?
I'm a daughter of a wealthy family
from the beginning.
But why do I have to lose the man I like?
Why do I have to lose everything?
That is all mine. Mine.
No.
No, you're wrong.
You blamed me for giving you...
a ragged underskirt.
But it wasn't like I gave you that...
while I myself had good ones.
I did everything I could.
I gave you the best things
I could possibly get.
I couldn't buy you anything as good
as those Eun Seo had.
But I put all my heart into the clothes...
whenever I bought them for you.
Sin Ae.
Now let it all go.
And make up with Eun Seo.
Will you do that, Sin Ae?
No.
No!
Sin Ae!
Sin Ae.
Jun Seo'll be back soon from school.
Are you his sister?
Would you like tea?
I'm fine.
Then...
And now...
we have to stay as brother and sister.
Jun Seo,
I love you.
What is this about?
I heard they called
Eun Seo and Tae Seok too.
Did they?
Jun Seo, why don't we tell them
about our wedding today?
Can you get off first?
Can you check out the trunk?
Will you marry me?
I'll do everything for you.
You will all be part of our family soon.
The reason we called you all to come...
Honey.
Eun Seo.
My daughter, Eun Seo.
Jun Seo, Sin Ae.
What is going on?
We...
have decided to adopt Eun Seo.
Our Eun Seo.
You'll be our real daughter.
No, you can't.
That's not going to happen.
Do you know about Jun Seo and Eun Seo?
They love each other.
They are in love.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
Who loves whom?
Who? Whom?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Look at this yourself.
Jun Seo, you...
You...
Dad, no.
It's not his fault.
I'm the one who loves him.
He doesn't love me back.
Jun Seo.
What does this all mean?
Is it true?
Is this true?
Yes.